女孩: 嘿，納特！
GIRL: Hey, Nat!
我們都是顛倒的。
We're both upside down.
我打賭你會先倒下。
And I bet you're gonna fall down first.
不你會的。
No, you will.
你撐不了多久了。
You can't hold it much longer.
我說過你會先摔倒的。
Told you you'd fall down first.
我告訴過你，我告訴過你！
I told you! I told you!
我就說嘛！
Told you so!
媽媽！
Mommy!
發生了什麼？
What happened?
她跪倒在地。
She fell on her knee.
你撞到膝蓋了?嗯。
Oh, you bump your knee? YOUNG YELENA: Mmmhmm.
哦..。
Oh...
別這樣，小傢伙。
Oh, come on, little one.
起來，你沒事了。
Get up. You're okay.
來吧，你是個勇敢的女孩。
Come on. You're a brave girl.
你的痛苦只會讓你更強大。
Your pain only makes you stronger.
對吧你?是啊。
Right, you? Yeah.
梅琳娜: 是嗎? 小葉琳娜: 看！
MELINA: Yeah? YOUNG YELENA: Look!
森林之星。
Forest stars.
是啊，你知道嗎？
MELINA: Yeah. You know what?
它們實際上是毒蛾科的一部分。
Those are actually part of the Lampyridae family.
你所看到的光芒,
And the glow, the glow that you see,
來自一種叫做... 的化學反應。
that comes from a chemical reaction called...
生物發光。
bioluminescence.
來吧，該吃晚飯了。
Come on, time for dinner.
年輕的葉琳娜: 生物腸胃素？
YOUNG YELENA: Biogoominfeasants?
梅麗娜: 「生物古敏菌」，沒錯。
MELINA: "Biogoominfeasants." That's right.
晚餐！
Dinner!
來吧，吃晚飯，大姑娘！
Come on, dinner, big girl!
我要芝士通心粉。
YOUNG YELENA: I want mac and cheese.
你想吃芝士通心粉?好吧我想..。
Oh, you want mac and cheese? Okay. Well, I want...
魚子醬和香檳。
caviar and champagne.
拿上餐巾紙。
Grab the napkins.
你拿著這個謝謝。
You take this. Thank you.
你能幫爸爸拿一下沙拉醬嗎？
Oh, would you grab the ranch dressing for Dad?
好吧。
Okay.
葉連娜: 青豆是我最喜歡的蔬菜。
YOUNG YELENA: Green beans are my favorite vegetable.
爸爸回來了！
Dad's home!
嘿爸爸。
Hey, Dad.
嘿寶貝。
Hey, baby.
一切都好嗎？
Everything okay?
大家今天過得怎麼樣？
ALEXEI: How was everybody's day?
小葉連娜: 媽媽教我關於燈蟲的知識。
YOUNG YELENA: Mommy taught me about lamp bugs.
我摔傷了膝蓋,
And I fell and hurt my knee,
但現在不疼了嗯。
but it doesn't hurt anymore. ALEXEI: Mmmhmm.
小葉連娜: 我們還在後院看到了螢火蟲。
YOUNG YELENA: And we also saw fireflies in the backyard.
這是我最喜歡的部分
That was my favorite part
一整天不。
of the whole day. No.
娜塔莎: 葉蓮娜，我們每年都能看到螢火蟲。
YOUNG NATASHA: Yelena, we see fireflies every year.
我們還有多少時間？
How long do we have?
我不知道大概一個小時吧。
I don't know. Like, an hour, maybe.
我不想去。
I don't wanna go.
別這麼說。
Don't say that.
姑娘們..。
Girls...
你還記得我告訴過你有一天我們會有一次大冒險嗎？
you remember when I told you that one day we would have that big adventure?
就是今天了耶！
Today's the day. Yay!
好吧，我們走。
All right, let's go.
對不起。
I'm sorry.
快點，我們得快點謝謝。
MELINA: Come on, we gotta hurry. ALEXEI: Thank you.
我沒穿鞋謝謝寶貝。
I don't have my shoes. ALEXEI: Thank you, baby.
沒關係，你不需要鞋子。
That's okay. You don't need your shoes.
但我還是很餓是嗎? 你猜怎麼著？
But I'm still hungry. Yeah? Guess what?
我車裏有水果卷。
I got Fruit RollUps in the car.
不，別管了，別管了，去車裏等著。
No, leave it, leave it, leave it. Go wait in the car.
你拿到了?是的。
You have it? Yeah.
這是唯一的一份?這是唯一一份沒著火的。
It's the only copy? It's the only one not on fire.
我們要去哪兒？
Where are we going?
家。
Home.
媽媽，你真傻。
YOUNG YELENA: Mommy, you're silly.
我們剛離開家。
We just left home.
我要我的歌。
I want my song.
再見，再見，美國派小姐
Bye, bye, Miss American Pie
把我的雪佛蘭開到堤壩，但堤壩是乾的
Drove my Chevy to the levee but the levee was dry
那些老好人喝著威士忌和黑麥威士忌
Them good old boys were drinking whiskey and rye
唱著，「這將是我死去的那一天」
Singing, "This'll be the day that I die"
」這將是我死的那一天」
"This'll be the day that I die"
梅麗娜: 快點，葉蓮娜。快點，寶貝。
MELINA: Come on, Yelena. Hurry up, baby.
走吧，快點，納特，快點，我們得走了。
Let's go. Come on, Nat. Hurry up. We gotta go.
我們得走了，快點，你得跑了。
We gotta go. Come on, you gotta run.
來吧，親愛的，親愛的。
Come on. Honey, honey.
跟你媽媽走跟你媽媽走好的。
Go with your mom. Go with your mom. Okay.
納特，快點!我來了！
MELINA: Nat, hurry up! I'm coming!
好的，安全帶。
MELINA: Okay. Seat belts.
好吧。
Okay.
娜塔莎: 爸爸為什麼不在飛機上？
YOUNG NATASHA: Why isn't Dad in the plane?
他來了，他來了，寶貝，他來了。
He's coming. He's coming, baby. He's coming.
媽媽？
Mom?
媽媽！
Mom!
我需要你上來。
I need you up here.
好的好的。
Okay. Okay.
我需要你向右轉。
I need you to pull right.
媽媽，你身上有血。
Mom, you've got blood on you.
沒事的寶貝。
It's okay, baby.
踩下那裏的油門。
Hit the accelerator there.
穩住，穩住。
Hold it steady, hold it steady.
你要以55節的速度後退。
You're gonna pull back at 55 knots.
讓我們一起數數。
Let's count together.
娜塔莎和梅麗娜: 45,50... ..。
YOUNG NATASHA AND MELINA: 45, 50...
撤退，你能做到的！
Pull back. You can do it!
退後，用盡全力。
Pull back. All your strength.
好的。
ALEXEI: Okay.
起來，媽媽。
YOUNG YELENA: Get up, Mommy.
痛苦只會讓你更強大，記得嗎？
Pain only makes you stronger, remember?
紅色衛報回來了。
The Red Guardian returns.
紅色衛報》凱旋歸來。
The Red Guardian returns triumphant.
求你了，求你了，不要再做臥底了。
Please, please, I beg you. No more undercover work.
我想重新投入戰鬥，我想要回我的西裝。
I wanna get back in the action. I want my suit back.
我想重新開始。
I wanna get back in it.
德雷科夫將軍，已經三年多了。
General Dreykov, it's been over three years.
永遠不要讓他們奪走你的心。
Never let them take your heart.
你拿到了嗎？
Did you get it?
那麼北方學院呢？
And the North Institute?
灰燼。
Ashes.
不會有事的。
It's gonna be okay.
梅麗娜怎麼樣了？
DREYKOV: How is Melina?
她會活下來的，她很強壯。
ALEXEI: She'll live. She's strong.
媽媽?媽媽？
YOUNG YELENA: Mommy? Mom?
爸爸!我來處理。
YOUNG YELENA: Daddy! I'll handle this.
爸爸! 爸爸!伊蓮娜！
Daddy! Daddy! Yelena!
爸爸!離她遠點！
Daddy! Get away from her!
別碰她！
Don't touch her!
我要把你們都殺了！
I will kill you all!
親愛的。
Honey.
你得把槍給我。
You're gonna need to hand me that gun.
我不想回去。
I don't wanna go back there.
我想留在俄亥俄州。
I wanna stay in Ohio.
你不能帶走她。
You can't take her.
你不能。
You can't.
她才六歲。
She's only six.
你那時更年輕。
ALEXEI: You were even younger.
沒關係。
It's okay.
過來。
Come here.
你會沒事的。
You're gonna be all right.
你知道為什麼會沒事嗎？
Do you know why it's gonna be all right?
因為我的姑娘們是世界上最堅強的姑娘。
'Cause my girls are the toughest girls in the world.
你們要互相照顧，好嗎？
You're gonna take care of each other, okay?
一切都會好起來的。
And everything, everything's gonna be fine.
德雷科夫: 那個，她身上有火焰。
DREYKOV: That one, she has fire in her.
她叫什麼名字？
What was her name?
娜塔莎。
ALEXEI: Natasha.
德雷科夫: 啊... 娜塔莎。
DREYKOV: Ah... Natasha.
不！
No!
清除所有的缺陷。
Remove all the defects.
那個
That one
還有她。
and her.
不！
YOUNG YELENA: No!
娜塔莎: 葉蓮娜！
YOUNG NATASHA: Yelena!
拿著! 拿著! 不！
Take it! Take it! No!
不！
No!
德雷科夫: 紅房間現在是你的家了。
DREYKOV: The Red Room is your home now.
娜塔莎: 放開我! 不！
YOUNG NATASHA: Get off me! No!
電視記者: 我們社區的臥底間諜。
TV REPORTER: Undercover spies in our communities.
他們使用假身份甚至養家餬口。
They took on false identities, even raised families...
他們在上面，長官!第一層有敵人！
AGENT 1: They're topside, sir! AGENT 2: Tier 1 has LOS!
我們已經封鎖了所有出口。
We've got all exits covered.
好的保持警惕。
All right. Stay alert.
我派阿爾法小隊過去。
I'm sending in alpha squad.
黑寡婦組織違反了索科維亞協議。
Natasha Romanoff is in violation of the Sokovia Accords.
她襲擊了 Wakanda 國王。
She assaulted the king of Wakanda.
殺雞儆猴。
Make an example out of her.
是嗎?別這樣。
Yeah? Don't do this.
做什麼？
Do what?
跟我來。
Come after me.
我是說，你在讓自己難堪，看起來很絕望。
I mean, you're embarrassing yourself. It looks desperate.
我還以為你會打電話給我來達成協議。
Thought maybe you'd be calling me to cut a deal.
因為從我的角度來看,
'Cause from my vantage point,
是那個聯邦逃犯
it's the federal fugitive
絕望的人。
who's desperate.
娜塔莎: 從我的角度來看，你看起來需要臥床休息。
NATASHA: From my vantage point, you look like you could use some bed rest.
這算什麼，你第二次做心臟搭橋手術？
What is this, your second triple bypass?
我不會擔心我自己。
I wouldn't worry about me.
我們有巴頓，還有威爾遜和另外一個傢伙,
We got Barton, we got Wilson and that other guy,
難以置信的縮水犯。
the incredible shrinking convict.
羅傑斯在逃，你沒有朋友。
Rogers is on the run. You got no friends.
你要去哪裏？
Where you gonna go?
在遇見你之前我經歷過很多次，羅斯。
I've lived a lot of lives before I met you, Ross.
你不用這麼麻煩的，我受夠了。
You shouldn't have gone to all this trouble. I'm done.
羅曼諾夫？
Romanoff?
空巢了，羅斯部長。
Got an empty nest, Secretary Ross.
她的追蹤器，長官。
Her tracker, sir.
盯住目標，等待包裹。
Eyes on target. Waiting for the package.
我已經瞄準了一個平行目標。
I have sights on collateral one.
代替三號發射。
Firing in place of three.
五，四..。
Five, four...
她發現我們了，目標放出煙霧。
WOMAN: She made us. Target deployed smoke.
她帶著包裹步行，站高點，我去地面。
She's on foot with the package. Stay high. I'm going to ground.
女名女子名。
Oksana.
哦，不。
Oh, no.
我做了什麼？
What did I do?
釋放其他人。
OKSANA: Free the others.
Yelena 我們需要一份狀態報告。
Yelena, we need a status report.
向隊長匯合。
Converge on team leader.
德雷科夫將軍，我們有個逃兵。
General Dreykov, we have a deserter.
是否允許激活任務主協議？
Permission to activate Taskmaster Protocol?
微笑。
Smile.
你在我的床上。
You're in my bed.
我... 我甚至都沒蓋被子。
I'm... I'm not even under the covers.
我單子上的東西你都買齊了嗎？
Did you get everything on my list?
有護照入境簽證還有幾張當地的駕照。
Got passports, entry visas, a couple of local driver's licenses.
混合搭配，你應該能夠延伸到20個左右的身份。
Mix and match, you should be able to stretch it to 20 or so identities.
范妮 · 隆巴頓？
Fanny Longbottom?
什麼?什麼，你才12歲？
What? What, are you 12?
外面有個發電機。
We've got a generator outside.
它是汽油動力的化糞池幾周後需要衝水,
It's petrolpowered. And the septic tank will need a flush in a couple of weeks,
但是，你知道，我已經找到了一個傢伙來為那。
but, you know, I've got a guy coming for that.
你得把垃圾運到城裏去，開車只要20分鐘。
You have to haul your rubbish into town. It's just a 20minute drive.
我把你的基本硬體裝備藏在樓梯下面了。
I've got your basic hardware kit stashed under the stairs.
很好。
Nice.
你還好嗎？
Are you okay?
為什麼不呢？
Why wouldn't I be?
我聽說了一些關於復仇者聯盟離婚的事。
I hear things. You know, something about the Avengers getting divorced...
沒關係。
Ugh. It's fine.
事實上我自己更好。
I'm actually better on my own.
你確定嗎？
Are you sure?
是的。
Yeah.
因為你可以告訴我。
Because you can tell me, you know.
朋友之間就是這樣的。
That's the way the whole friends thing works.
我知道我有朋友。
I know. I have friends.
有朋友的人不會打電話給我。
People who have friends don't call me.
我付錢不是讓你擔心的。
And I don't pay you to worry.
哦嘿。
Oh, hey.
這些垃圾是什麼？
What's all this junk?
只是一些布達佩斯安全屋的信件和私人物品。
Oh, just some mail and personals from the Budapest safe house.
布達佩斯？
Budapest?
是的，布達佩斯。
Yeah. Budapest.
不是布達佩斯布達佩斯。
No, it's "Budapest." Budapest.
布達佩斯。
Budapest.
是」布達佩斯」隨便啦。
It's "Budapest." Whatever.
我知道你不會回去，所以我現在在公寓裏安排了別人。
I knew you weren't going back there, so I've got someone else in the flat now.
抱歉讓你費這麼大勁，我會讓你扔掉的。
Sorry you went through the trouble. I would've told you to chuck it.
好吧，如果你不想要，就把它扔進垃圾桶。
Well, if you don't want it, throw it in the rubbish.
你不是運動員，邦德先生。
HUGO DRAX: You're not a sportsman, Mr. Bond.
你為什麼要破壞這次會面
Why did you break up the encounter
和我的寵物蟒蛇一起？
with my pet python?
因為我發現他喜歡我。
Because I discovered he had a crush on me.
墾月者一號準備發射。
Moonraker 1 on preset launch program...
太好了。
Oh, great.
... 減去兩分鐘。
...minus two minutes.
收回船員通道..。
Retract crew access...
我很確定羅斯在這裏沒有管轄權。
I'm pretty sure Ross has no jurisdiction here.
你應該知道我生氣的時候槍法更準。
And you should know I'm a better shot when I'm pissed off.
你不是來找我的。
You're not here for me.
該死。
Oh, shit.
我知道你在外面。
I know you're out there.
娜塔莎: 我知道你知道我在這裏。
NATASHA: I know you know I'm out here.
那你為什麼鬼鬼祟祟的，好像這裏是雷區一樣？
YELENA: Then why are you skulking about like it's a minefield?
娜塔莎: 因為我不知道能否信任你。
NATASHA: 'Cause I don't know if I can trust you.
有意思，我也想說同樣的話。
Funny, I was going to say the same thing.
娜塔莎: 那麼，我們要像成年人一樣談話嗎？
NATASHA: So, we gonna talk like grownups?
我們就是這樣嗎？
Is that what we are?
放下槍，否則我要你好看。
Put it down before I make you.
你把槍放下。
You put yours down.
小心腳下
Watch your step.
趴下趴下。
Stay down. Stay down.
趴下趴下
Stay down.
你非得來布達佩斯不是嗎？
You had to come to Budapest, didn't you?
我來這裏是因為我以為你不會。
I came here because I thought you wouldn't.
但既然你在這裏，什麼子彈能做到這一點？
But since you're here, what bullet does that?
不是子彈，是箭。
Not bullets. Arrows.
啊，對。
Ah, right.
如果你認為我不會來這裏，為什麼還寄這個給我？
If you didn't think I'd come here, why'd you send me this?
你把它帶回來了？
You brought it back here?
我不是來和你做朋友的，但你得告訴我那是什麼。
I'm not here trying to be your friend, but you need to tell me what that is.
這是一種合成氣體。
YELENA: It's a synthetic gas.
化學抑制劑化學抑制的中和劑。
The counteragent to chemical subjugation.
這種氣體免疫了大腦的神經通路
The gas immunizes the brain's neuropathways
來自外部操縱。
from external manipulation.
下次用英語怎麼樣？
Maybe in English next time?
你為什麼不把它帶給你的超級科學家朋友呢？
Why don't you take it to one of your superscientist friends?
他們可以解釋給你聽。
They can explain it to you.
也許是托尼 · 斯塔克？
Tony Stark, maybe?
我們現在不怎麼說話所以..。
Oh, yeah. We're not really talking right now, so...
太好了來得正是時候。
Great. Perfect timing.
當你需要一個復仇者的時候，他在哪裏？
Where's an Avenger when you need one?
我不想待在這裏。
I don't wanna be here.
我在逃命，你差點害死我。
I'm on the run. You could've gotten me killed.
那我該怎麼辦？
Well, what was I supposed to do?
你是我認識的唯一一個超級英雄。
You're the only superhero person that I know.
這就是我寄給你的全部原因。
That was the whole reason I sent it to you.
我一直在看新聞,
I kept checking the news,
希望看到美國隊長打敗紅廳。
expecting to see Captain America bringing down the Red Room.
什麼？
What?
拿下紅房間? 你在說什麼？
Taking down the Red Room? What are you talking about?
已經消失好幾年了。
It's been gone for years.
德雷科夫死了。
Dreykov's dead.
我殺了他。
I killed him.
你不會真的相信吧？
You don't actually believe that, do you?
你真的這麼認為。
You really do believe that.
德雷科夫死了。
Dreykov's dead.
為了找到他，我差點毀了整個城市。
It took almost destroying the entire city just to get to him.
如果你這麼肯定，那就告訴我發生了什麼。
If you're so sure, then tell me what happened.
準確地告訴我。
Tell me exactly.
我們安裝了炸彈。
We rigged bombs.
」我們」是誰?克林特 · 巴頓。
Who's "we"? Clint Barton.
殺死德雷科夫是我叛逃到神盾局的最後一步。
Killing Dreykov was the final step in my defection to S.H.I.E.L.D.
就這麼簡單？
Simple as that?
當然」簡單」
Yeah, sure, "simple."
這就是我所說的五層樓的內爆
That's what I'd call imploding a fivestory building
然後和匈牙利特種部隊一起射擊。
and then shooting it out with the Hungarian Special Forces.
我們躲了10天才逃出布達佩斯。
Took 10 days in hiding before we could even get out of Budapest.
你檢查了屍體？
And you checked the body?
確認殺人了嗎？
Confirmed the kill?
沒有屍體留下來檢查。
There was no body left to check.
你忘了德雷科夫的女兒。
You're forgetting Dreykov's daughter.
娜塔莎: 我們要去哪裏？
NATASHA: Where are we trying to get?
葉連娜: 摩托車! 大樓東側。
YELENA: Motorbike! East side of the building.
我抓住你了！
I got you!
不!
No!
嘿。
Hey.
別動，你受傷了。
Don't move. You're hurt.
我來幫你。
Let me help you.
你在幹什麼?他逼我的。
What are you doing? He's making me.
你現在相信我了嗎？
Do you believe me now?
還有多少人？
How many others?
夠了。
Enough.
娜塔莎: 哪一個是你的？
NATASHA: Which one's yours?
黑色，棕色的座位。
Black. Brown seat.
我的鑰匙呢？
Where are my keys?
隨時都有可能。
Any day now.
你不能偷別人的車。
You can't just steal a guy's car.
所以你想讓我追蹤他然後取消偷竊？
So you want me to chase him down and unsteal it?
好的，請隨時開始閉嘴。
Okay. Any time now, please. Shut up.
好吧你有個計劃,
Okay, you got a plan,
還是繼續躲躲藏藏？
or shall I just stay duckandcover?
是的，我的計劃是把我們趕走。
Yeah, my plan was to drive us away.
這計劃爛透了。
That's a shit plan.
舉手之勞，何足掛齒。
You're welcome.
該死，他回來了。
Oh, shit. He's back.
繫上安全帶。
Put your seat belt on.
你真是個好媽媽。
You're such a mom.
娜塔莎，不。
YELENA: Natasha, no.
我想我在流血，我..。
I think I'm bleeding. I'm...
不現在不行相信我。
No. Not now, trust me.
你還好嗎？
You okay?
好主意。
Yeah. Great plan.
我喜歡我差點流血而死的那部分。
I love the part where I almost bled to death.
這裏很舒適。
This is cozy.
巴頓和我在這裏躲了兩天。
Barton and I spent two days hiding out up here.
那一定很有趣。
That must have been fun.
那傢伙到底是誰？
Who the hell is that guy?
德雷科夫的特別項目。
Dreykov's special project.
他可以模仿任何他見過的人。
He can mimic anyone he's ever seen.
這就像和鏡子搏鬥一樣。
It's like fighting a mirror.
德雷科夫只有在最重要的任務時才會派遣他。
Dreykov only deploys him for toppriority missions.
這沒有任何意義。
This doesn't make any sense.
當你忽略關鍵細節的時候，事實很難說得通。
Well, the truth rarely makes sense when you omit key details.
這是什麼意思？
What is that supposed to mean?
你一個字都沒提過德雷科夫的女兒。
You didn't say one word about Dreykov's daughter.
你殺了她。
You killed her.
我必須這麼做。
I had to.
我需要她帶我找到德雷科夫。
I needed her to lead me to Dreykov.
我們需要確認德雷科夫在大樓裏。
We need confirmation Dreykov's in the building.
娜塔莎: 他的車現在停下來了。
NATASHA: His car is pulling up now.
德雷科夫的女兒是附帶傷害。
Dreykov's daughter was collateral damage.
我需要她的確認。
I needed her to be sure.
娜塔莎，明白了嗎？
Natasha, we clear?
一切正常。
All clear.
而你在這裏，卻不那麼確定。
And here you are, not so sure.
我需要出去走走。
I needed out.
紅房間還在運行，它在哪裏？
The Red Room's still active. Where is it?
我不知道。
I have no idea.
他經常搬家。
He moves location constantly.
每個寡婦在出入境時都要服用鎮靜劑，以獲得最高安全級別。
And every widow is sedated on entry and exit for maximum security.
我只是覺得很難相信他能躲開我的視線。
I'm just finding it hard to believe that he could stay off my radar.
如果你想躲起來就攻擊復仇者是不明智的。
Well, it's not smart to attack an Avenger if you want to stay hidden.
線索就在名字裏。
I mean, the clue is in the name.
德雷科夫殺了你,
Dreykov kills you,
其中一個大人物會來為你報仇。
one of the big ones comes to avenge you.
等等，大的是什麼？
Wait, what are the big ones?
好吧，我懷疑來自太空的上帝在戰鬥後一定要服用布洛芬。
Well, I doubt the god from space has to take an ibuprofen after a fight.
你以為我這段時間在哪兒？
Where did you think I was all this time?
我以為你出獄了，過著正常的生活。
I thought that you got out and were living a normal life.
然後你就再也沒聯繫過她？
And you just never made contact again?
說實話我以為你不想見我。
Honestly, I thought you didn't wanna see me.
胡說八道。
Bullshit.
你只是不想你的小妹妹跟著你,
You just didn't want your baby sister to tag along,
同時你和酷小孩拯救了世界。
whilst you saved the world with the cool kids.
你不是我真正的妹妹。
You weren't really my sister.
復仇者並不是你真正的家人。
And the Avengers aren't really your family.
你為什麼總是這樣做?做什麼？
Why do you always do that thing? NATASHA: Do what?
你們吵架的時候要做的事。
The thing you do when you're fighting.
那個... 那個..。
The... Like, the...
你做的這件事
This thing that you do
當你在打架的時候甩動你的頭髮
when you whip your hair when you're fighting
手臂和頭髮。
with the arm and the hair.
然後你擺出一個打鬥的姿勢。
And you do, like, a fighting pose.
這是個打架的姿勢，你完全是個裝腔作勢的人。
It's a fighting pose. You're a total poser.
我不是裝腔作勢的人
I'm not a poser.
拜託這些姿勢都很棒,
Oh, come on. I mean, they're great poses,
但你覺得大家都在看著你,
but it does look like you think everyone's looking at you, like,
一直。
all the time.
我花了那麼多時間擺造型，其實是想做點好事
All that time that I spent posing, I was trying to actually do something good
來彌補我們帶來的痛苦。
to make up for all the pain and suffering that we caused.
試著不僅僅是一個訓練有素的殺手。
Trying to be more than just a trained killer.
那你是在自欺欺人
Well, then you were fooling yourself
因為痛苦和折磨每天都在發生，而我們都是訓練有素的殺手。
because pain and suffering is every day and we are both still a trained killer.
只是我不是雜誌封面上的那個人。
Except I'm not the one that's on the cover of a magazine.
我不是那種被小女孩們稱為英雄的殺手。
I'm not the killer that little girls call their hero.
那種氣體,
That gas,
反作用劑,
the counteragent,
它是秘密合成的
it was synthesized in secret
梅麗娜那一代的一個老寡婦。
by an older widow from Melina's generation.
我在執行取回它的任務，而她暴露了我
I was on the mission to retrieve it, and she exposed me
我殺了釋放我的寡婦。
and I killed the widow that freed me.
你有選擇嗎？
Did you have a choice?
你所經歷的是心理調節。
What you experienced was psychological conditioning.
我說的是化學改變大腦功能。
I'm talking about chemically altering brain functions.
它們完全是兩碼事。
They're two completely different things.
你完全有意識，但是你不知道哪一部分是你自己。
You're fully conscious, but you don't know which part is you.
我還是不確定。
I'm still not sure.
就剩這些了?嗯哼。
Is that all there is left? Mmmhmm.
只有這樣才能阻止德雷科夫和他的寡婦網絡。
It's the only thing that can stop Dreykov and his network of widows.
他每天都吃得更多。
He takes more every day.
沒有人保護他們的孩子。
Children who don't have anyone to protect them.
就像我們小時候一樣。
Just like us when we were small.
也許20個人中就有一個能在訓練中存活下來，成為寡婦。
Maybe one in 20 survives the training, becomes a widow.
剩下的，他殺人。
The rest, he kills.
對他來說，我們只是東西。
To him, we are just things.
沒有臉的武器，他可以隨便扔掉。
Weapons with no face that he can just throw away.
因為總會有更多。
Because there is always more.
沒人在找他多虧了你和阿列克謝。
And no one's even looking for him, thanks to you and Alexei.
娜塔莎: 阿列克謝?
NATASHA: Alexei?
YELENA: 「爸爸。」
YELENA: "Dad."
你有沒有找過你的父母? 你真正的父母？
YELENA: Did you ever look for your parents? Your real ones?
我媽把我像垃圾一樣丟在街上。
Well, my mom abandoned me in the street like garbage.
你呢？
What about you?
他們毀了我的出生證明，所以我重新發明了它。
They destroyed my birth certificate, so I reinvented it.
我父母還住在俄亥俄州。
My parents still live in Ohio.
我妹妹搬到西部去了。
My sister moved out west.
是這樣嗎？
Is that right?
你是個科學老師。
You're a science teacher.
不過你現在是兼職工作，尤其是在你有了兒子之後。
You're working parttime, though, especially after you had your son.
你丈夫，他負責裝修房子。
Your husband, he renovates houses.
這不是我的故事
That is not my story.
你的故事是什麼？
What is your story?
我從來沒有讓自己獨處足夠長的時間去思考它。
I never let myself be alone long enough to think about it.
你有沒有想過要孩子？
Did you ever wish for kids?
我想要一隻狗。
I want a dog.
你要去哪裏？
Where you gonna go?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我真的沒有地方可以回去了,
I don't really have anywhere to go back to,
所以我猜隨便哪裏都行。
so I guess anywhere.
不要不要什麼？
Don't. Don't what?
你要給我一些大英雄的演講,
You're going to give me some big hero speech,
我能感覺到。
I can feel it.
我不擅長演講。
Speeches aren't really my thing.
哈。
Huh.
這更像是一種邀請。
It was more like an invitation.
去紅房間殺掉德雷科夫？
To go to the Red Room and kill Dreykov?
是的。
Yeah.
儘管紅房間很難找到
Even though the Red Room is impossible to find
德雷科夫太狡猾殺不了人嗎？
and Dreykov is too slippery to kill?
是的。
Yeah.
聽起來工作量很大。
That sounds like a shitload of work.
不過應該會很有趣。
Could be fun, though.
是的。
Yup.
我看到他把鑰匙放哪兒了。
I saw where he put the keys.
最上面的抽屜，綠色的櫃子。
Top drawer, green cabinet.
你知道嗎，這是第一件
You know, this is the first piece of clothing
買給自己的最好的禮物。
I've ever bought for myself.
那個？
That?
是啊，你不喜歡？
Yeah. You don't like it?
那是不是像..。
Is that like a...
是軍隊剩餘還是..。
Is it army surplus, or...
好吧，它有很多口袋。
Okay, it has a lot of pockets.
但我一直在用,
But I use them all the time,
我自己做了一些修改。
and I made some of my own modifications.
隨便啦。
Whatever.
閉嘴重點是我從沒..。
Shut up. The point is, I've never...
我以前從來沒有控制過自己的生活，現在我做到了。
I've never had control over my own life before, and now I do.
我想做一些事情。
I want to do things.
娜塔莎: 嗯... ..。
NATASHA: Hmm...
我喜歡你的背心。
I like your vest.
我就知道，我就知道，很酷吧？
I knew it. I knew you did. It's so cool, right?
很好，是的，我喜歡。
It's good. Yes. I like it.
你可以在裏面放很多東西，你甚至不會知道。
And you can put so much stuff in there. You wouldn't even know.
不過我真的不知道紅房間在哪裏。
I really don't know where the Red Room is, though.
對不起我知道。
I'm sorry. I know.
但我想我知道有人知道。
But I think I know somebody who does.
是嗎? 誰？
Oh, yeah? Who?
我們需要一架飛機。
We're gonna need a jet.
我說我們需要一架飛機。
I said we needed a jet.
你知道你沒給我什麼嗎? 時間。
Yeah, you know what you didn't give me? Time.
或者錢，我不是飛機做的。
Or money. I'm not made of jets.
我以為你是最棒的。
YELENA: I thought you were supposed to be the best.
像個真正的專業人士。
Like a real pro.
哦，對不起，皇后。
Oh, I beg your pardon, tsarina.
是免費的公寓和終身供應的基塞爾
Was the free flat and lifetime supply of kissel
你不喜歡?哈！
not to your liking? Ha!
娜塔莎: 別讓她把你惹毛了。
NATASHA: Don't let her wind you up.
不，我反對質疑我的專業性。
No, I take exception to impugning my professionalism.
你確實給我安排了一個六小時後就壞掉的發電機。
Well, you did set me up with a generator that crapped out after six hours.
你也是哈?雙人搭檔。
You, too, huh? Tag team.
哦，他很敏感，看看你為什麼把他留在身邊。
Aw, he's sensitive. See why you keep him around.
娜塔莎: 其他的呢？
NATASHA: Where's the rest?
就是這樣。
Voila.
耶倫娜: 哦。
YELENA: Ooh.
我大概五年前藏起來的。
Oh, I stashed that, like, five years ago.
怎麼樣？
How is it?
很乾，真的很乾。
It's dry. It's really dry.
你知道，你有一個危險接近的時間來結清你的賬單。
You know, you're getting dangerously close to running out your tab.
物資我可以統計但你得引起當局的注意,
Supplies I can tally, but you bring me attention from the authorities,
我的價格都上漲了。
all my prices go up.
那是什麼意思？
What's that supposed to mean?
你的朋友，羅斯部長，一直在打聽我的事
Your mate, Secretary Ross, has been sniffing around my affairs
直到我的聯繫人拒絕我的電話。
to the point at which I've got contacts declining my calls.
我是個私人承包商。
I'm a private contractor.
你很敏感。
You are sensitive.
你真是個討厭的傢伙。
You're a very annoying individual.
我會補償你的嗯。
I'll make it up to you. Mmmhmm.
你每次都這麼說。
That's what you say every time.
所以，我有核密碼。
So, I have the nuclear code.
但他就在那兒。
But there he is.
美國隊長!美國。
Captain America! INMATES: America.
紅色衛士的時代終於來臨了！
Finally, the Red Guardian's time has come!
我抓住他的盾牌
I grab hold of his shield
面對面，這是對力量的考驗。
and face to face, it's a test of strength.
哦... 哦，不。
Oh... Oh, no.
哦..。
Oh...
那傢伙以為他能打敗我。
That guy think he going to beat me.
不管怎樣，這個盾牌，你知道，他隨身帶著
Anyway, this shield, you know, that he carries with him
就像寶寶的毯子，你知道嗎？
like a precious baby blanket, you know?
我利用這一點，我利用這一點
I use it to my advantage. I take it
我把他推出窗外。
and I push him out the window.
然後我就逃走了？
And I make my escape. Huh?
今年是哪一年？
What year was this?
我不知道，大概83,84年吧。
I don't know. Like, '83, '84.
我知道。
I know.
那時的美國隊長還被冰凍著。
Captain America was still frozen in ice then.
你是在說我是個騙子嗎，爾薩？
Are you calling me a liar, Ursa, huh?
哦，不。
Oh, no.
啊哦。
Uhoh.
看那隻大熊。
Aw, look at the big bear.
要哭了嗎，小姑娘？
Gonna cry, little girl?
今天是你的幸運日，阿列克謝。
Today is your lucky day, Alexei.
到南邊牆上的門那裏去。
Move to the door on the south wall.
左轉。
Go left.
只是別大吵大鬧。
Just don't make a scene.
你把事情鬧大了，是不是？
You made a scene, didn't you?
現在怎麼辦？
What now?
我們要帶你離開這裏。
We're gettin' you outta here.
到上面一層去。
Go to the upper level.
快點，超級戰士。
Move your ass, super soldier.
他不可能成功的。
He's never going to make it.
靠近點。
Get me closer.
你有更好的主意嗎？
You got a better idea?
娜塔莎。
ALEXEI: Natasha.
裝腔作勢的傢伙。
Such a poser.
真的嗎？
Seriously?
喔！
Whoo!
對不起！
Sorry!
你在幹什麼? 開什麼玩笑？
What are you doing? Are you kidding me?
退後！
Back up!
我們都做得很好。
YELENA: We're both doing a really good job.
沒有。
No.
好了夠了。
Okay. Enough of this.
哈！
Ha!
哇..。
Whoa...
這將是一個很酷的死法。
This would be a cool way to die.
告訴我這對我們來說是個好兆頭！
Tell me that's a good sign for us!
快點！
Move your ass!
快救我們出去！
Get us outta here!
哈。
Huh.
等等！
Wait!
太好了！
Yes!
我這裏需要幫助！
I need some help up here!
哦，真令人興奮。
Oh, that was exciting.
我真為你們感到驕傲。
Oh, I'm so proud of you girls.
你聽不見我說話？
Oh, you can't hear me, huh?
好吧。
Okay.
哇。
Wow.
好吧。
Okay.
為什麼這麼咄咄逼人？
Why the aggression, huh?
這是你每月的大姨媽嗎？
Is it your time of the month?
我沒來例假，笨蛋，我沒有子宮。
I don't get my period, dipshit. I don't have a uterus.
或者卵巢。
Or ovaries.
是啊，這就是紅房間
Yeah. That's what happens when the Red Room
讓你做非自願子宮切除術。
gives you an involuntary hysterectomy.
它們就這麼進去，然後把你所有的生殖器官都扯出來。
They kind of just go in and they rip out all of your reproductive organs.
他們就這麼衝進去，把他們都剁了。
They just get right in there and they chop them all away.
所有東西都拿出來了所以你不能生孩子好了好了好了好了！
Everything out, so you can't have babies. ALEXEI: Okay, okay. Okay! Okay!
你沒必要這麼客觀和下流。
You don't have to get so clinical and nasty.
我正要說到
Oh, well, I was about to talk about
輸卵管不過沒關係沒有。
fallopian tubes, but okay. ALEXEI: No.
你回來救我對我來說意義重大。
It means so much to me that you came back for me.
不，不，你得告訴我們怎麼去紅房間。
No. No. You're gonna tell us how to get to the Red Room.
哈。
Huh.
哇，看看你，哈? ，都是生意。
Whoa, look at you, huh? All business.
相信我，這不是快樂。
Trust me, this isn't pleasure.
小娜塔莎，全都被灌輸進了西方的議事日程。
Little Natasha, all indoctrinated into the Western agenda.
我選擇去西部成為一名復仇者。
I chose to go west to become an Avenger.
因為他們視我如家人。
'Cause they treated me like family.
真的嗎? 家人？
ALEXEI: Really? Family?
他們現在在哪兒？
Well, where are they now?
那家人現在在哪兒？
Where is that family now?
告訴我紅房間在哪裏。
Tell me where the Red Room is.
我不知道
I have no idea.
好嗎？
ALEXEI: Okay?
拜託你和德雷科夫就像..。
Come on. You and Dreykov were like...
德雷科夫?是的。
Dreykov? Yeah.
德雷科夫將軍，我的朋友？
General Dreykov, my friend, huh?
給我榮耀..。
Gives me glory...
蘇聯第一個也是唯一一個超級士兵。
Soviet Union's first and only super soldier.
我本可以比美國隊長更出名。
I could have been more famous than Captain America.
然後他把我埋在俄亥俄去執行那個愚蠢的任務。
Then he buries me in Ohio on that stupid mission.
三年！
Three years!
太無聊了，讓我無聊到流淚。
So tedious, boring me to tears.
無意冒犯？
No offense, huh?
然後讓我在監獄裏度過餘生，為什麼？
Then puts me in prison for the rest of my life. Why, huh?
為什麼? 為什麼他要把我放進... 你知道為什麼嗎？
Why? Why would he put me in... You know why?
因為也許我想談談國家的衰落。
'Cause maybe I want to talk about the withering of the state.
或者也許我不喜歡他的頭髮什麼的
Or maybe I don't like his hair or something
我隨口說了幾句。
and I say something casually about that.
也許，你知道,
Maybe, you know,
我想讓這個派對感覺像個真正的派對
I want the Party to feel actually like a party
而不是這個討厭的組織。
instead of this sourpuss organization.
但事實並非如此。
But instead, no.
他讓我在監獄裏度過餘生。
He puts me in prison for the rest of my life.
他就這麼跑掉躲起來了？
He just runs off and hides, huh?
我甚至不是那個..。
I'm not even the one who, uh, you know...
又不是我殺了他女兒。
I'm not the one who killed his daughter.
我們現在能把他扔出窗外嗎？
Can we throw him out the window now?
我認為我們應該等到更高的海拔再行動。
I think we should wait till we get to a higher altitude.
好吧。
All right.
等等，梅琳娜媽媽？
Wait, Mom Melina?
我們以為她死了
We thought she was dead.
那麼快的狐貍是殺不死的。
You cannot kill a fox that swift.
噁心什麼？
Ew. ALEXEI: What?
她是科學家，戰略家，我是打手。
She was the scientist, the strategist. I was the muscle.
她直接為德雷科夫工作的次數比我多得多。
She worked directly for Dreykov far more than I ever did.
等等，你是說梅麗娜現在在紅房間工作？
Wait. Are you telling me that Melina is working for the Red Room present day?
她在聖彼得堡城外遠程工作。
She works remotely outside St. Petersburg.
呃..。
Uh...
我想我們沒有足夠的燃料去聖彼得堡。
I don't think we have enough fuel for St. Petersburg.
不用了，我們可以的。
No, we're good. We'll make it.
好吧。
Okay.
你應該帶上復仇者的超級噴氣機。
You should've brought the Avengers' superjet.
我發誓如果我再聽到他說一個字,
I swear, if I hear one more word from him,
我會踢他的臉他是最壞的。
I will kick him in the face.  He's the worst.
娜塔莎。
ALEXEI: Natasha.
娜塔莎娜塔莎。
Natasha. Natasha.
過來，我想問你點事。
Come here, I want to ask you something.
來吧，這很重要什麼？
Come, it's important. What?
他跟你提起過我嗎？
Did he talk to you about me?
什麼？
What?
他跟你提起過我嗎? 你知道，交換戰爭故事？
Did he talk to you about me? You know, trading war stories?
誰? 你在說什麼？
Who? What are you talking about?
美國隊長。
Captain America.
在這個地緣政治衝突的舞台上，我最大的對手。
My great adversary in this theater of geopolitical conflict.
與其說是復仇女神。
Not so much a nemesis.
更像一個現代人，你知道嗎? Coequal。
More like a contemporary, you know? Coequal.
我一直認為我們之間有很多相互尊重。
I always thought there was a great deal of mutual respect...
等等你都20年沒見過我們了
Wait. You haven't seen either one of us in 20 years
你要問我關於你的事嗎？
and you're gonna ask me about you?
這種緊張關係是怎麼回事？
What is with this tension?
我做錯什麼了嗎？
Did I do something wrong?
這是個嚴肅的問題嗎？
Is that a serious question?
我只愛過你們，姑娘們。
I only ever loved you girls.
我盡最大努力確保你會成功
I did my best to make sure you would succeed
充分發揮你的潛能,
to achieve your fullest potential,
一切都解決了一切都解決了？
and everything worked out. Everything worked out?
是的對你來說是的。
Yes. For you, yes.
我們在俄亥俄州完成了任務。
We accomplished our mission in Ohio.
葉蓮娜，你繼續成為最偉大的兒童殺手
Yelena, you went on to become the greatest child assassin
世界上最偉大的人。
the world has ever known.
沒有人能比得上你的效率，你的冷酷無情。
No one can match your efficiency, your ruthlessness.
還有娜塔莎,
And Natasha,
不僅僅是間諜不僅僅是推翻政權,
not just a spy, not just toppling regimes,
從內部摧毀帝國,
destroying empires from within,
而是復仇者。
but an Avenger.
你們兩個都殺了
You both have killed
這麼多人。
so many people.
你的賬本一定在滴水，血流成河。
Your ledgers must be dripping, just gushing red.
我真為你感到驕傲。
I couldn't be more proud of you.
好吧你可以... 不。
Okay. You can... No.
放開我。
Let go of me now.
你聞起來真臭。
You smell really bad.
那麼，我們到了嗎？
So, are we there yet?
我們到了你就知道了。
You'll know when we're there.
輕微右轉。
MELINA: Slight right.
直走。
Straight on.
對。
Right.
輕微右轉。
Slight right.
非常好，親愛的。
Oh, very good, my darling.
是的，非常好。
Yes, very good.
是的，非常好，親愛的
Yes, very good, my darling.
回到安全的地方，快點，快走。
Back home where it's safe. Come on. Go on.
親愛的我們回來了。
Honey, we're home.
來吧姑娘們。
Come on, girls.
歡迎光臨寒舍。
Welcome to my humble abode.
不要拘束。
Make yourself at home.
娜塔莎: 嘿，別耍花招。
NATASHA: Hey, no funny business.
我要放下武器。
I am putting away my weapon.
娜塔莎: 這附近有陷阱嗎？
NATASHA: Are there any booby traps around here?
有什麼我們需要知道的嗎？
Anything we need to know about?
我養育我的女兒們不是為了讓她們落入陷阱。
I didn't raise my girls to fall in traps.
你根本沒有撫養我們長大。
You didn't raise us at all.
也許吧。
Oh, maybe so.
但是如果你變軟弱了，那就不是在我的監視下。
But if you got soft, it wasn't on my watch.
我們喝酒吧。
Let's drink.
好的。
ALEXEI: Okay.
還是很合適。
Still fits.
天啊。
Oh, my God.
梅麗娜: 我一次也沒洗過。
MELINA: I never washed it once.
過來喝一杯。
Come and drink.
起來吧，你們這些拯救者
Rise, you workers of salvation
家庭
Family
重新聚在一起。
back together again.
嗯鑒於我們
Mmm. Seeing as our
家庭結構
family construct
只是一個計劃好的詭計只持續了三年,
was just a calculated ruse that only lasted three years,
我想我們不能再用這個詞了，對吧？
I don't think that we can use this term anymore, can we?
同意接下來這麼辦。
Agreed. So, here's what's gonna happen...
好吧，那就再聚一次，嗯？
Okay. A reunion then, huh?
還有..。
And, uh...
我想馬上說點什麼。
I want to say something right off the bat.
你一點都沒變老，是吧？
You haven't aged a day, huh?
你就像他們安排我們結婚那天一樣美麗溫柔。
You're just as beautiful and as supple as the day they staged our marriage.
梅麗娜: 你變胖了。
MELINA: You got fat.
但還是不錯的
But still good.
我剛從監獄出來。
I just got out of prison. I, uh...
我精力充沛哦！
I have a lot of energy. MELINA: Oh!
請不要這樣做。
Please don't do that.
接下來是這樣的。
So, here's what's gonna happen.
娜塔莎，別垂頭喪氣的。
Natasha, don't slouch.
我沒有無精打采不，你有。
I'm not slouching. MELINA: Yes, yes, you are.
我並不懶散。
I don't slouch.
你會得到一個背部隆起。
You're going to get a back hunch.
聽你媽媽的話娜塔莎: 哦，天哪，這..。
Listen to your mother. NATASHA: Oh, my God, this...
起來，起來。
Up, up.
好了，夠了，你們所有人。
All right, enough. All of you.
我什麼都沒說，這不公平。
I didn't say anything. That's not fair.
事情是這樣的...我不想吃東西。
Here's what's gonna happen... I don't want any food.
梅麗娜: 吃點東西吧，葉連娜，看在上帝的份上。
MELINA: Eat a little something, Yelena, for God's sake.
你得告訴我們紅房間的位置。
You're gonna tell us the location of the Red Room.
就像你告訴他們
You know, it's like when you told them
他們可以熬夜抓聖誕老人。
that they could stay up late to catch Santa Claus.
什麼? 那很有趣，你知道，「他從煙囪下來，姑娘們。
What? That was fun. You know, "He come down the chimney, girls.
「小心，他在哪兒?」
"Look out. Where is he?"
你等著他等餅乾吃完,
You wait for him, and then when the cookies are gone,
然後你看到他在那裏。
then you see he's there.
不不什麼我想要
No, no. What? I want them
去追尋他們的夢想不好。
to follow their dreams. MELINA: No good.
追求明星吧，姑娘們。
ALEXEI: Reach for the stars, girls.
找到德雷科夫不是幻想，而是未竟的事業。
Finding Dreykov is not a fantasy. It's unfinished business.
你無法打敗一個支配他人意志的人。
You can't defeat a man who commands the very will of others.
你永遠看不到我們在美國開始的事業的頂峰。
You never saw the culmination of what we started in America.
你也沒有。
Nor did you.
娜塔莎，集中注意力，集中注意力，得到你想要的。
Natasha, always focus, focus. Get what you want.
進來吧。
Come in.
那頭豬剛才開門了嗎？
Did that pig just open the door?
是的。
Yes. It did.
好孩子，阿列克謝，好孩子。
Good boy, Alexei. Good boy.
你用我的名字給一頭豬命名？
You named a pig after me?
你不覺得這很像嗎？
You don't see the resemblance?
看，他像狗一樣坐著。
See, he sits just like dog.
太棒了，現在，看著。
Amazing. Now, watch.
對我來說有點奇怪。
ALEXEI: It's a little weird, to me.
停止呼吸。
Stop breathing.
我們滲透進了俄亥俄州的北方研究所。
We infiltrated the North Institute in Ohio.
那是神盾局科學家的掩護。
It was a front for S.H.I.E.L.D. scientists.
事實上，當時的科學家是九頭蛇。
Actually, it was Hydra scientists at that time.
結合冬兵計劃,
In conjunction with the Winter Soldier project,
他們解剖並解構了人類的大腦
they had dissected and deconstructed the human brain
創造了第一個也是唯一一個基底神經節的細胞藍圖。
to create the first and only cellular blueprint of the basal ganglia.
是認知的樞紐。
Was the hub for cognition.
自主運動，程序性學習。
Voluntary motor movement, procedural learning.
我們沒有竊取武器或技術。
We didn't steal weaponry or technology.
我們偷走了釋放自由意志的鑰匙。
We stole the key to unlocking free will.
你在幹什麼？
What are you doing?
我在解釋現在的科學是如此精確,
Oh, I am explaining that the science is now so exact,
可以指示實驗對像停止呼吸
the subject can be instructed to stop breathing
除了服從別無選擇。
and has no choice but to obey.
好了，你說得夠清楚了，夠了。
Okay, you made your point. That's enough.
是的，好吧，別擔心，阿列克謝本來可以活下來的
Yes, all right. Well, don't worry, Alexei could've survived
還有11秒沒有氧氣。
11 more seconds without oxygen.
好孩子，現在你回家去，回到安全的地方。
Good boy. Now, you go back, back home where it's safe.
你回去，回家，回到安全的地方。
You go. You go back home, back home where it's safe.
好孩子，阿列克謝。
Good boy, Alexei.
當世界被控制的時候，它就在一個更高的層次上運作。
The world functions on a higher level when it is controlled.
德雷科夫用化學方法征服了遍佈全球的間諜。
Dreykov has chemically subjugated agents planted around the globe.
你知道他們在誰身上測試嗎？
And do you know who they test it on?
梅麗娜: 嗯..。
MELINA: Hmm...
不，那不是我的部門。
No. That's not my department.
啊，快點，快點。
ALEXEI: Ah, come on, come on.
別對他們撒謊我沒撒謊。
Don't lie to them. Hmm? I'm not lying.
你是德雷科夫的建築師？
You're Dreykov's architect, huh?
梅麗娜: 你是什麼？
MELINA: What were you?
如果我是他的建築師，你就是他的搭檔。
If I was his architect, you were his partner.
你是他的生意夥伴。
You were his business partner.
不，不，不，我是替罪羊！
No, no, no. I was patsy!
別跟我說...他向我兜售意識形態。
Don't give me that... He sell me ideology.
別再談政治了一直以來更大的..。
Stop with the politics. All the while, bigger...
閉嘴! 你是個白癡。
Shut up! You are an idiot.
你是個懦夫。
And you're a coward.
You're a coward.
我們的家庭從來都不是真實的，所以沒有什麼可以堅持的。
And our family was never real, so there's nothing to hold on to.
我們繼續前進。
We're moving on.
從來沒有家人，是吧？
ALEXEI: Never family, huh?
在我心裏，我是個單純的人。
In my heart, I am simple man.
我覺得對於一對深入臥底的俄羅斯特工來說
And I think that for a couple deep undercover Russian agents
我覺得我們做父母做得很好，是吧？
I think we did pretty great as parents, huh?
是的，我們有我們的命令，我們完美地扮演了我們的角色。
Yes, we had our orders, and we played our roles to perfection.
誰在乎? 那不是真的。
Who cares? That wasn't real.
什麼?那不是真的，誰在乎？
What? That wasn't real. Who cares?
別這麼說。
Don't say that.
別這麼說，那是真的。
Please don't say that. It was real.
這對我來說是真實的，你是我的母親。
It was real to me. You are my mother.
你是我的親生母親。
You were my real mother.
我曾經擁有的最接近的東西。
The closest thing I ever had to one.
我生命中最美好的部分是虛偽的。
The best part of my life was fake.
你們都沒告訴我。
And none of you told me.
還有那些特工
And those agents
你用化學方法征服了全球？
you chemically subjugated around the globe?
那就是我。
That was me.
嗯。
Mmm.
而你，你逃出來了。
And you, you got out.
德雷科夫確保沒有人能逃脫。
Dreykov made sure no one could escape.
你要說什麼嗎？
Are you gonna say anything?
沒有。
No.
別碰我。
Don't touch me.
葉蓮娜。
Yelena.
沒有。
No.
我不知道沒事沒事。
I had no idea. It's okay, it's okay.
我去和她談談。
I'll go talk to her.
我進來是因為我不想說話。
I came in here because I didn't want to talk.
好吧。
Okay.
我們... 我們只是坐著。
We, uh... We just sit.
我們只是坐著。
We just sit.
你要去哪兒？
Where are you going?
我自己來不行你活不下去的。
To do this myself. Don't. You won't survive.
我希望我能相信你在乎我。
I wish I could believe that you cared.
但你不是第一個拋棄我的母親。
But you're not even the first mother that abandoned me.
不，你不是被拋棄的。
No, you weren't abandoned.
你被一個程序選中了
You were selected by a program
評估嬰兒的基因潛能。
that assessed the genetic potential in infants.
我被帶走了？
I was taken?
我相信交易達成了，你的家人得到了回報。
I believe a bargain was struck, your family paid off.
但是你媽媽，她一直在找你。
But your mother, she never stopped looking for you.
她在那方面和你很像她是的
She was like you in that way. She was
無情的。
relentless.
她怎麼了？
What happened to her?
德雷科夫殺了她。
Dreykov had her killed.
她的存在威脅著要揭開紅屋的面紗。
Her existence threatened to uncover the Red Room.
一般來說，一個好奇的平民的行為
Normally, the actions of one curious civilian
不會被處決,
wouldn't warrant an execution,
但是，正如我所說，她是無情的。
but, as I said, she was relentless.
我生命中的每一天都在想她。
I thought about her every day of my life.
不管我自己承認與否，我都承認了。
Whether or not I admitted it to myself, I did.
我一直覺得最好不要回顧過去。
I've always found it best not to look into the past.
那你為什麼還留著這個？
Then why did you save this?
我記得這一天。
I remember this day.
我們在一天之內拍攝了聖誕節、感恩節、復活節和暑假。
We shot Christmas, Thanksgiving, Easter and summer vacation all in one day.
不同的背景嗯。
Different backdrops. Mmm.
我知道樹下所有的禮物都是空盒子，但我不在乎。
I knew all the presents under the tree were just empty boxes, but I didn't care.
我想打開每一個..。
I wanted to open every single one...
所以哪怕只有一秒鐘，感覺都是真實的。
so just for a second it would feel real.
讓我們停止這一切。
Let's stop this.
你為什麼要這麼做？
Why you doing this?
為什麼一隻出生在籠子裏的老鼠會跑在那個小輪子上？
Why does a mouse born in a cage run on that little wheel?
你知道我騎車經過紅房間嗎
Do you know I was cycled through the Red Room
在你出生前四次？
four times before you were even born?
我只知道那些牆。
Those walls are all I know.
我從來沒有選擇的餘地。
I was never given a choice.
但你不是老鼠，梅麗娜。
But you're not a mouse, Melina.
你只是出生在一個籠子裏，但這不是你的錯。
You were just born in a cage, but that's not your fault.
告訴我，你是如何保住你的心的？
Tell me, how did you keep your heart?
痛苦只會讓我們更強大。
Pain only makes us stronger.
你沒告訴我們嗎？
Didn't you tell us that?
你教我的東西讓我活了下來。
What you taught me kept me alive.
對不起，我已經通知了紅房間。
I'm sorry, I already alerted the Red Room.
他們隨時會到。
They'll be here any minute.
阿列克謝: 所以，我和我的父親在那裏冰上釣魚。
ALEXEI: So, there I am ice fishing with my father.
這個小冰棚裏的天氣很冷。
It's very cold day in this little ice shed.
即使對俄羅斯來說也很冷，你知道嗎？
Cold even for Russia, you know?
「把伏特加留在火爐邊,」父親會對我說。
"Keep the vodka by the fire," my father would say to me.
請不要說話。
Please stop talking.
請等一下，請等一下請不要。
Please wait. Please wait. Please, no.
求你了，我不想說話。
Please, I don't want to talk.
求你了求你了。
Please. Please.
我告訴你這些是有原因的相信我。
There is a reason why I'm telling you this, okay? Trust me.
我正在抓魚。
I am reaching for fish.
哦! 我失去平衡了。啊！
Oh! I lose balance. Ah!
撲通一聲！
Splash!
我的手伸到河裏去了
My hands go in the river.
在這種天氣裏，凍傷很快就會發作。
In this weather, frostbite sets in quick.
我父親，他在我手上上廁所。
My father, he go toilet on my hands.
天啊。
Oh, my God.
尿液是35攝氏度，延緩凍傷。
Urine is 35 degrees Celsius, staves off the frostbite.
這有什麼關係？
How is this relevant?
你知道,
You know,
父親。
fathers.
不不。
No. No.
你什麼也沒做，只是告訴我你有多無聊。
You have done nothing but tell me how bored you were.
我是個累贅，你不想做的工作。
I was the chore, the job you didn't want to do.
對我來說？
To me?
對我來說，你就是一切。
To me, you were everything.
沒錯，你不在乎，你不在乎。
Exactly. You don't care. You don't care.
你唯一在乎的就是你那愚蠢的光輝歲月
The only thing you care about are your stupid glory days
就像深紅髮電機一樣，沒有人願意聽到這個消息。
as the Crimson Dynamo, and no one wants to hear about it.
是紅色衛報。
It's the Red Guardian.
出去。
Get out.
滾出去！
Get out!
我不記得了
I can't remember
如果我哭了
If I cried
當我讀到他的寡婦新娘的故事時
When I read about his widowed bride
有些東西深深地觸動了我的內心
Something touched me deep inside
那一天
The day
音樂
The music
死了
Died
他們在唱歌
And they were singing
再見再見
Bye Bye
美國派小姐美國派
Miss American Pie American Pie
把我的雪佛蘭開到堤壩上
Drove my Chevy to the levee
但堤壩是幹的是干的
But the levee was dry Was dry
他們都是好孩子
Them good old boys
喝威士忌
Drinking whiskey
唱歌
Singing
雙方: 「這將是一天，我死」
BOTH: "This will be the day that I die"
「就是這一天... ...」
"This'll be the day..."
趴下。
Get down.
他們認為..。
They think...
對不起。
I'm sorry.
別讓他久等了。
Let's not keep him waiting.
請求降落許可。
MELINA: Request clearance for landing.
梅麗娜？
Melina?
我們一分鐘後著陸。
We're touching down in one minute.
那我們為什麼還要上去？
Then why are we still going up?
現在你該知道這些年德雷科夫是怎麼躲過雷達的監視的了。
Now you'll know how Dreykov stayed above the radar all these years.
德雷科夫: 我的天。
DREYKOV: My God.
那麼呃,
So, uh,
家庭聚會怎麼樣？
how was the family reunion?
太可怕了。
Oh, it was awful.
他們很粘人,
They were clingy,
而且太情緒化，太粘人了
and too emotional, and needy.
就像以前一樣?嗯。
Just like old times, huh? Hmm.
葉蓮娜 · 貝洛娃。
Yelena Belova.
她是怎麼回事？
What's the deal with her?
她是唯一一個受影響的，對嗎？
She was the only one affected, right?
據我所知，是的。
As far as I know, yes.
這些氣體和解毒劑,
These gasses and antidotes,
真讓我頭疼。
it's a pain in my ass.
這是個問題，你需要解決它。
It's a problem. You need to sort it.
嗯，我有九頭豬
Hmm. I have nine pigs
需要在我不在的時候處理。
that will require attending to in my absence.
別管你的豬了。
Don't give a shit about your pigs.
把她的腦袋挖出來。
Cut her brain out...
找出弱點。
Hmm? Identify the weakness.
這種死法就沒那麼酷了。
This is a much less cool way to die.
男名男子名。
Alexei.
梅麗娜: 那羅曼諾夫呢？
MELINA: What about Romanoff?
她是個叛徒。
She's a traitor.
她背叛了她的人民，背叛了她的血統。
She turned her back on her people. On her blood.
她一無所有。
She had nothing.
我給了她家我給了她愛。
I gave her home. I gave her love.
把你做的那個東西放進她體內。
Put that thing in her you do.
你知道，化學藥品。
You know, uh, chemicals.
把她變成你的豬。
Turn her into one of your pigs.
你能想像我能控制一個復仇者做什麼嗎？
Can you imagine what I could do with an Avenger under my control?
你不想先和她談談嗎？
Wouldn't you like to speak to her first?
當你看著你撫養長大的孩子的眼睛,
When you look into the eyes of a child you have raised,
世界上任何面具都無法掩蓋這一點。
no mask in the world can hide that.
歡迎回家。
Welcome home.
現在，現在。
Now, now.
別把我的新玩具弄壞了。
Don't go breaking my new toy.
娜塔莎。
Natasha.
我救不了我們。
I can't save us.
我想讓你知道我很抱歉。
I need you to know that I'm sorry.
我為了一個目標而獻出了生命。
I pledged my life to a cause.
我以為我很勇敢。
You know, I thought I was being very brave.
可能是最勇敢的。
Possibly the bravest.
但我並不勇敢。
But I wasn't being brave.
我是個懦夫。
I was coward.
在古巴,
In Cuba,
當他們把你從我身邊帶走的時候..。
when they came and took you away from me...
沒有任何理由值得你這麼做。
No cause is worth that.
你只應該犧牲你自己
You should only sacrifice yourself
為了什麼...
for something...
你是怎麼做到的？
How did you do that?
這些細胞是我自己設計的。
I designed these cells myself.
什麼？
What?
我向你袒露了我的靈魂，而你一直都是我的唯一？
I bared my soul to you and it was just you the whole time?
是的，恐怕是這樣。但是，等等，噓，我在和葉琳娜通話。
Yes, I'm afraid so. But wait, shh, I'm on comms with Yelena.
葉蓮娜，是我，媽媽。
Yelena, it's me. It's Mama.
你的腰帶裏藏著一把兩英吋長的刀片。
You have a twoinch blade concealed in your beltline.
什麼？
What?
你要對我做什麼？
What are you going to do to me?
梅麗娜: 右臀外側。
MELINA: Outside right hip.
你就不能早點告訴我嗎？
You couldn't have told me sooner?
梅麗娜: 不要大發雷霆。
MELINA: Don't throw a fit.
沒時間了好了姑娘們,
There wasn't time. Okay, girls,
我聽不清你說什麼,
I'm having trouble hearing you,
但是，娜塔莎，有些事情我需要你知道。
but, Natasha, there's something I need you to know.
我要你知道我很抱歉別再找借口了好嗎？
I need you to know that I'm sorry. No more excuses, okay?
我為了事業獻出了生命，我以為我很勇敢。
I gave my life for a cause. I thought I was being brave.
你沒有耳機。
You don't have earpiece.
什麼？
What?
不，她聽不見。
No, she can't hear you.
你沒有耳機為什麼？
You don't have earpiece. Why not?
因為這不是計劃的一部分。
Because it wasn't part of the plan.
哦，是嗎? 那麼，你的計劃是什麼？
Oh, yeah? Well, what was the plan?
娜塔莎: 那麼，一旦我們進去了,
NATASHA: So, once we're inside,
我激活我的追蹤器，羅斯就會跑過來。
I'll activate my tracker and Ross will come running.
你知道你仍然是一個全球性的逃犯，是嗎？
You are aware that you are still a global fugitive, yes?
你瞭解這個設施，一定有辦法讓它著陸。
You know the facility. There must be some way to land it.
讓他們把我們關在零層。
Instruct them to confine us on level zero.
一旦我出去了我就可以啟動著陸協議,
Once I'm out, I can activate the landing protocol,
我們可以在一小時內降落。
we can descend within the hour.
啊有問題。
Ah, problem.
我只有一個耳機。
I only have one earpiece set.
我會把它交給葉蓮娜。
I'll give it to Yelena.
他把藥瓶帶到哪裏去了？
Where did he take the vials?
梅麗娜: 可能去冷藏室了。
MELINA: Probably down to cold storage.
德雷科夫仍然控制著寡婦們,
Dreykov still has the widows under his control,
所以你必須讓他們接觸解毒劑。
so you have to expose them to this antidote.
是的，當然，放鬆。
Yeah. Sure. Easy.
這就是你的計劃嗎？
Is this your plan?
我的計劃是殺了你。
My plan is to kill you.
我還活著。
I'm alive.
那我們現在怎麼辦？
So, what do we do now?
我母親叫什麼名字？
What was my mother's name?
啊..。
Ah...
我們埋葬她的地方,
Where we buried her,
有一棵樹..。
there was a tree...
嗯..。
Um...
一朵粉紅色的花。
A pink blossom.
真漂亮。
Beautiful.
還有一塊墓碑
And there was a tombstone
上面刻著她的名字。
with her name engraved on it.
她叫什麼名字？
What was her name?
「未知。」
"Unknown."
你什麼都感覺不到嗎？
You don't feel anything?
我殺你女兒的時候你有什麼感覺嗎？
You feel anything when I killed your daughter?
這就是你鬧鬼的過去嗎？
Is this your haunted past?
謝謝你，娜塔莎。
Thank you, Natasha.
你給了我最強大的武器。
You gave me my greatest weapon.
打個招呼。
Say hello.
當你的炸彈爆炸時,
When your bomb exploded,
它差點殺了我的安東妮亞。
it nearly killed my Antonia.
我不得不在她脖子後面植入芯片。
I had to put a chip in the back of her neck.
在她脖子後面。
In the back of her neck.
看看她。
Look at her.
你覺得看著她很難受嗎？
You find it difficult to look at her?
我知道。
I do.
她... 她什麼都看
She... She watches everything
她能做到。
and she can do it.
她是個完美的模仿者。
She's a perfect mimic.
她就像你所有的朋友一樣打架。
And she fights just like all of your friends.
她能聽見我說話嗎？
Can she hear me?
什麼？
What?
你想讓她好受點嗎？
You want to make her feel better?
你想告訴她你很抱歉嗎？
You want to tell her you're sorry?
在你打爆她的臉之前你就該想到這一點。
Well, you should have thought of that before you blew her face off.
但是這些廢話已經夠多了。
But enough of all this bullshit.
去工作吧。
Go to work.
地下室有老鼠，快去。
I have rats in the basement. Go.
去吧。
Go.
那是個錯誤。
Well, that was a mistake.
是嗎？
Was it?
你剛剛送走了唯一能阻止我殺你的東西。
You just sent away the one thing that would stop me from killing you.
那就試試吧。
Try, then.
動手吧。
Do it.
保險開著嗎？
Is the safety on?
沒有。
No.
試試你的刀
Try your knife.
德雷科夫: 啊... ..。
DREYKOV: Ah...
你有麻煩了。
You're in trouble.
你是怎麼控制我的？
How are you controlling me?
我沒有控制你，娜塔莎。
I'm not controlling you, Natasha.
好吧，還沒有。
Well, not yet.
但是有一種信息素鎖。
But there is a pheromonal lock.
聞到我的信息素，你就不會對我動粗了。
Smelling my pheromones prevents you from committing violence against me.
我很生梅麗娜的氣。
I'm very upset with Melina.
真遺憾我不得不殺了她。
It's a shame I have to kill her.
拜託，如果我們只是想
ALEXEI: Come on, now. If we're just going to
按下按鈕，黑進電腦..。
press buttons and hack computers...
是的我是說，我不知道。
MELINA: Yes. ALEXEI: I mean, I don't know.
我無能為力。
There's nothing for me to do.
我想... 我想打碎什麼東西。
I want to... I want to break something.
是嗎?是的
Oh, you do?
有東西是可以打破的。
Oh, there is something you can break.
Melina 如果這是我們最後一次..。
Melina, if this is the last time that we...
該死。
Ah, damn it.
太噁心了。
That was disgusting.
好吧。
Okay.
這就是你的大計劃？
So, this was the big plan, huh?
梅麗娜準備降落在紅房間，把我交給當局。
Melina was going to land the Red Room and hand me over to the authorities.
不不不。
Oh, no, no, no.
那麼，現在怎麼辦，你要把我捲進你那可悲的木偶戲裏嗎？
So, what now, you're gonna fold me into your pathetic little puppeteer act?
真可悲，是吧？
Pathetic, huh?
是啊，你會怎麼說？
Yeah, what would you call it?
我會稱之為...最後一次
I would call it... When was the last time
你和某人談過話
that you had a conversation with somebody
不是被迫跟你說話的人嗎？
that wasn't forced to talk to you?
你跑去打一場錯誤的戰爭。
You ran away to fight in the wrong war.
真正的戰爭是在這裏打的，在暗處。
The real war was fought here, in the shadows.
你沒有在暗處戰鬥。
You didn't fight in the shadows.
你躲在黑暗中。
You hid in the dark.
真正的力量來自於無法察覺的影響力。
Real power comes from undetectable influence.
如果沒有人注意到，那為什麼還要這麼做呢？
If no one's noticed, then why even do it?
你什麼都不是。
You're nothing.
嗯你什麼都沒有。
Hmm. You have nothing.
這個星球上有50個人..。
There are 50 people on this planet...
別說了。
Oh, stop it.
別叫我停下來！
Don't tell me to stop!
如果我不告訴你什麼時候該停止，那麼你怎麼知道什麼時候該閉嘴呢？
If I don't tell you when to stop, then how will you know when to shut up?
來吧。
Come on.
你以為我挨不了一拳？
Think I can't take a punch?
哦
DREYKOV: Oh.
該死的你太軟弱了軟弱？
God damn it, you're weak. Weak?
我打賭在毫無防備的小女孩面前強硬起來會更容易，對吧？
I bet it's easier to be tough in front of defenseless little girls, huh?
夠了
DREYKOV: That's enough.
德雷科夫: 你不會這麼油嘴滑舌
DREYKOV: You wouldn't be so glib
如果你知道我建造了什麼的話。
if you had any notion of the scope of what I've built.
我擁有這個世界，我。
I own this world. Me.
你似乎不顧一切地想給我留下好印象。
You seem desperate to impress me.
我不需要給你留下深刻印象。
I don't need to impress you.
我不需要給任何人留下好印象。
I don't need to impress anyone.
這些世界領袖，這些偉人,
These world leaders, these great men,
她們聽命於我和我的寡婦們。
they answer to me and my widows.
看看他們。
Look at them.
這些女孩都是垃圾。
These girls were trash.
他們被扔到街上。
They are thrown out into the street.
我回收垃圾。
I recycle the trash.
我給了他們目標。
And I give them purpose.
我給了他們生活。
I give them a life.
梅琳娜，我找到那些瓶子的位置了。
Melina, I found the location of the vials.
梅麗娜: 我遇到了一點小挫折。
MELINA: I've had a slight setback.
你得去找那些寡婦。
You'll need to get to the widows.
德雷科夫: 這是我的寡婦網
DREYKOV: It's my network of widows
幫助我控制權力的天平。
that help me control the scales of power.
一個命令，石油和股票市場崩潰。
One command, the oil and stock markets crumble.
只要一個命令，地球上四分之一的人就會挨餓。
One command, and a quarter of the planet will starve.
我的寡婦們可以發動和結束戰爭。
My widows can start and end wars.
他們可以製造國王，也可以摧毀國王。
They can make and break kings.
你在這裏控制一切？
You control all of that from here?
和你在一起,
And with you,
一個由我控制的復仇者,
an Avenger under my control,
我終於可以走出陰影了
I can finally come out of the shadows
利用世界上僅有的自然資源。
using the only natural resource that the world has too much of.
女孩們。
Girls.
都是從那個小控制台？
All from that little console?
德雷科夫: 是的。
DREYKOV: Yeah.
你覺得這很好笑嗎？
Oh, you find this amusing?
你笑什麼？
Why are you smiling?
不是針對你但是..。
Don't take it personal, but, uh...
謝謝你的合作。
Thank you for your cooperation.
即使你找到了數據庫讓他給你看鑰匙,
Even if you locate the database and get him to show you the key,
你不能從他那裏拿走。
you won't be able to take it from him.
多年來，德雷科夫實施了一種信息素鎖
For years, Dreykov has implemented a pheromonal lock
所有的寡婦，包括我。
in all widows, even me.
所以，只要我們能聞到他的氣味，我們就不能傷害他。
So, as long as we can smell him, then we won't be able to hurt him.
我還是屏住呼吸吧。
Well, I'll just hold my breath.
還不夠。
Not enough.
這是基礎科學。
This is basic science.
娜塔莎，為了阻斷嗅覺中樞的受體,
Natasha, to block receptors in olfactory center,
你必須切斷神經。
you have to sever the nerve.
我能搞定。
I can handle that.
你不夠強壯所以..。
You weren't quite strong enough, so...
我得自己完成它。
I'll have to finish it myself.
你打算怎麼辦？
What are you going to do?
切斷神經。
Sever the nerve.
梅麗娜！
Melina!
這正是我所想的。
Precisely what I was thinking.
葉蓮娜，計劃有點小變動。
Yelena, slight change of plan.
我徹底摧毀了其中一個引擎，我們即將墜毀。
I completely demolished one of the engines and we are going into a controlled crash.
葉琳娜: 太棒了。
YELENA: Fantastic.
我現在去找寡婦們。
I'm heading to the widows now.
沒有。
No.
梅麗娜: 我們得走了。
MELINA: We have to go.
你現在不太愛說話了，是嗎？
Not so talkative now, are you?
你奪走了我的童年。
You took my childhood.
你奪走了我的選擇，試圖擊垮我。
You took my choices and tried to break me.
但你再也不能這樣對待任何人了。
But you're never gonna do that to anybody ever again.
德雷科夫: 在她死之前，任何人不得離開這個房間。
DREYKOV: Nobody leaves this room until she's dead.
讓她痛苦。
Make her suffer.
我不想傷害你。
I don't wanna hurt you.
你不想傷害我。
You don't wanna hurt me.
嘿。
YELENA: Hey.
你還好嗎？
Are you okay?
看起來好像很疼。
That looks like it hurts.
好，我數到三就開槍，準備好了嗎？
Okay. I take out on three, ready?
對不起。
I'm sorry.
離開這裏越遠越好。
Get as far away from here as possible.
你現在可以自己做決定了。
You get to make your own choices now.
我們得離開這裏。
We gotta get outta here.
我們得找到德雷科夫，你來嗎？
We need to find Dreykov. Are you coming?
我就在你後面。
I'm right behind you.
等等，等等，我得回去！
Wait, wait! I have to go back!
太好了！
Yes!
你看到那些女孩了嗎？
Do you see the girls?
不！
No!
我們得回去。
We need to go back.
我們失去控制了。
MELINA: We've lost control.
女名女子名。
Antonia.
我去開門。
I'm gonna open the door.
你會來找我的。
You're gonna come after me.
沒事了，沒事了。
It's okay. It's okay.
我知道你還在裏面。
I know you're still in there.
我不會離開你的好嗎。
And I'm not gonna leave you. Okay.
葉蓮娜！
Yelena!
她在機翼上！
She's on the wing!
快走! 你們還在等什麼？
Move! What are you waiting for?
別這麼做！
Don't do it!
這很有趣！
This was fun!
不！
No!
好吧。
Okay.
我們走。
Let's go.
夠了。
Enough.
對不起。
I'm sorry.
他走了嗎？
Is he gone?
他走了。
He's gone.
葉蓮娜！
Yelena!
葉蓮娜？
Yelena?
我們都是顛倒的。
We're both upside down.
我應該回來找你的。
I should've come back for you.
你不用這麼說。
You don't have to say that.
沒事的嘿嘿。
It's okay. Hey. Hey.
這對我來說也是真實的。
It was real to me, too.
葉琳娜: 謝謝。
YELENA: Thank you.
大家都好嗎？
Everybody good?
我明顯受傷了。
I am clearly injured.
你有話要說嗎？
You got something to say?
我只會把事情搞砸。
I'd just mess it up.
騎兵來了。
Here comes the cavalry.
我們正在接近目標，長官。
We're closing in on the target, sir.
我們的計劃是什麼？
So, what's our plan?
你們去吧我留下。
You guys go. I'll stay.
這太瘋狂了，我們打架，我們和你一起打架。
That's insanity. We fight. We fight with you.
娜塔莎: 我來拖住他們。阿列克謝: 娜塔莎，我們戰鬥。
NATASHA: I'll hold them off. ALEXEI: Natasha, we fight.
梅麗娜: 我們不能分開。你太固執了。
MELINA: We can't split up. You're so pigheaded.
娜塔莎: 你們快走天啊。
NATASHA: You guys, go. Oh, my God.
而且如果我們四個能成功的話,
Besides, if it can work out with the four of us, you know,
復仇者聯盟或許還有希望。
there may be some hope for the Avengers.
一點點。
Little bit.
好吧，如果你要走的話，我想你應該拿著這個。
Okay, well, if you're leaving, then I guess you should take this.
我知道你有多喜歡。
I know how much you like it.
娜塔莎: 胡說
NATASHA: Shucks.
它確實有很多口袋。
It does have a lot of pockets.
非常方便的口袋。
Very handy pockets, yeah.
他在世界各地植入了寡婦。
He had widows implanted all over the world.
梅麗娜需要複製分子式,
Melina will need to copy the formula,
但你應該告訴他們一切都結束了。
but you should be the one to tell 'em it's over.
你回來救我們了。
You came back for us.
謝謝你。
Thank you.
梅麗娜: 嘿。
MELINA: Hey.
照顧好自己，好嗎？
Hey. You take care of yourself, okay?
別擔心，我來處理。
Don't worry. I got this.
我知道。
I know.
梅麗娜: 別擔心，我們會帶她一起去的。
MELINA: Don't worry. We're bringing her with us.
來，跟我們走。
Come. Come with us.
你從來不睡覺嗎？
You ever not sleep?
因為你，我在三天內穿越了六個時區。
I've been in six different time zones in three days because of you.
真的嗎?是的。
Oh, really? Yeah.
什麼，你是在拆零件嗎？
What, are you scrapping together some parts?
這次你給我買了什麼，一台倒置的割草機？
What'd you get me this time, like, an upsidedown lawnmower?
你看我花點時間和金錢就能給你弄到什麼？
You see what I can get you with a bit of time and money?
說啊，我想聽。
Go on, say it. I wanna hear it.
聽到這些對我來說真的很好，真的。
It would really be good for me to hear it. Really.
真讓我印象深刻。
I'm impressed.
是啊。
Well, yeah.
你一直是我的好朋友。
You've always been a really good friend to me.
這是每個男人都想聽到的。
That's what every man wants to hear.
你要去哪裏？
Where you gonna go?
真有意思，我這一輩子都以為自己沒有家人。
It's funny. My whole life, I didn't think I had any family.
結果我有兩個所以..。
Turns out I got two, so...
其中一個現在有點亂。
One of them's a bit of a mess right now.
我要把他們中的幾個從監獄裏救出來
I'm gonna go break a few of them out of prison
看看我能不能幫上忙。
see if I can't help patch things up.
我對中西部過敏。
I'm allergic to the Midwest.
這個女人的所作所為,
What this woman did,
說實話我都不敢想像。
honestly, I can't even imagine.
你不應該在我的假期打擾我，瓦倫蒂娜。
You're not supposed to be bothering me on my holiday time, Valentina.
哦，打擾你了? 哦，不，不。
Oh, bothering you? Oh, no, no.
我只是來表達我的敬意。
I'm just here paying my respects.
嗯... ..。
YELENA: Hmm...
來這裏讓你看起來很絕望。
You know, coming here makes you look desperate.
好吧。
Okay.
我要加薪。
I want a raise.
哦，是的，你和我都是。
Oh, yeah. You and me both.
相信我，這是你應得的。
Believe me, you're gonna earn it.
我找到你的下一個目標了。
I've got your next target.
我想親手交給你。
Thought I'd handdeliver it.
也許你想殺了那個害死你妹妹的人。
Maybe you'd like a shot at the man responsible for your sister's death.
挺可愛的，你不覺得嗎？
Kind of a cutie, don't you think?